musicinafrica.net 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Music In Africa

We are pleased that you are using our website and would like to thank you for your interest. Music In Africa ([www.musicinafrica.net](http://www.musicinafrica.net/)) is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our visitors. This policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**The type of information collected by Music In Africa**

The type of information collected by MIA is either information of a personal nature that you supply to us (such as your name address, email address, telephone number, company name etc), when you create an account, request for information, services and / or support, participate in surveys and the like; or content submitted by users in support of MIA’s vision to act as a platform for the sharing and exchange of information relating to the African music industry. See the MIA Terms of Use to see how contributions submitted as a way of sharing industry information or knowledge is dealt with.

  **Anonymous data collection**

You may, as a matter of principle, visit the Music In Africa portal [www.musicinafrica.net](http://www.musicinafrica.net/) without telling us who you are. We are notified merely of the name of your Internet Service Provider, the website from which you accessed our site, and which of our website pages you visit. This information is evaluated for statistical purposes and you anonymity as an individual user is preserved.

  **Cookies**

We may place a "cookie" on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to keep track of your choice of language and home page preference and to gather usage data that will help us generally improve the quality of our Website. Should you not want us to send you cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept cookies.

  **Use Of IP Address**

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to a computer whenever it is connected to the Internet.  We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to audit the use of the Web Site. We do not link IP addresses to personal information, which means that your session may remain anonymous.  However, the Owner cannot guarantee that this will always be the case.  For example, it may be necessary to identify a particular user when it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Terms and Conditions or to protect our service website or other interests.  
Personally Identifiable Information

  We may collect information that can be used to identify you (Personally Identifiable Information). Please note that we only collect Personally Identifiable Information when you specifically provide it to us such as to register for our newsletter or directory, in response to a survey or when registering for personal services. You may also be asked to create a user account and provide certain information including your name, email addresses, physical address, and telephone number. When you create a user account on our website and sign in to your account, you are not anonymous to us.

  **Using Your Personal Information**

Personal information submitted on the portal will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. The information  is generally used to process your requests and transactions, to ennsure that we provide you with the highest quality service possible, to interact with you regarding opportunities that may be of interest to you and to, as much as is possible, customize your experience on the site.

In particular we may use your personal information to:  
a. monitor the website;  
b. improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;  
c. enable your use of the services available on the website  
d. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested  
e. send to you our newsletter  
f. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and  
Note: The emails that we send contain links that enable you to "unsubscribe" from such mailings.

  **Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers or agents, insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:

a. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
b. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;  
c. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)

Except as provided for in this privacy policy and in our Terms Of Use, we will not provide, share, sell or rent your information to third parties.

**Security Of Your Personal Data**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. Data transmission over the internet is, however, inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

**Third Party Websites**

The portal contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**Variation**

This Privacy Policy is effective as at 15 January 2014. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We do not undertake to provide you with personal notice of any changes. In the event of material changes, we will provide notice by means that are reasonable under the circumstances, such as by posting a notice on the Websites. Your continued use of the Websites following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes.
